A Guide to the Virginia Auditor of Public Accounts - Pay claims for witnesses, 1857-1880
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
Virginia Auditor of Public Accounts - Pay claims for witnesses, 1857-1880
The Library of Virginia
APA 721
1.25 cu. ft. (3 boxes)
Virginia. Auditor of Public Accounts (1776-1928)
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Transferred from the Auditor of Public Accounts in 1913.
Scope and Content
This series consists of lists of pay claims filed on behalf of witnesses. The lists contain the defendants name and offence, name of witness, number of days attending, miles traveled, and aggregate amount of pay to which the witness was entitled.
These records are part of Auditor of Public Accounts. Disbursements to Localities and Individuals: Local Government Expenses - Criminal and Civil Prosecutions.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged alphabetically by folder title.
Contents List
- Accomack County, 1858-1860 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Defendants: Peter (a slave); and Nicholas Herring.
- Albemarle County, 1863 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Alexandria County, 1858 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  Defendants: Margaret Lucas; Julia Rush; William Smith; and John Murphy.
- Alleghany County, 1859 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Amherst County, 1859 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Augusta County, 1858, 1861 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Bath County, 1859-1861 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Barbour County, 1859 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Bedford County, 1859 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Berkley County, 1858 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Boone County, 1860 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Braxton County, 1858-1859 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Brooke County, 1857 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Brunswick County, 1858 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Calhoun County, 1859 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Carroll County, 1879-1880 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Charles City County, 1858 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Clay County, 1859-1860 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Dodridge County, 1861 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Fauquier County, 1859-1860 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Floyd County, 1860 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Frederick County, 1859, 1861 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Grayson County, 1859-1860 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Halifax County, 1860-1861, 1863 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Hampshire County, 1861 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Hanover County, 1858, 1860-1862 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Hardy County, 1858 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Harrison County, 1859-1860 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Henrico County, 1864 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Henry County, 1858, 1865 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Jackson County, 1858-1860 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Jefferson County, 1858-1859 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Kanawha County, 1859 (Box 1, Folder 33)
- King and Queen County, 1860 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Lee County, 1858, 1860 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Lewis County, 1858, 1860 (Box 1, Folder 36)
- Logan County, 1857 (Box 1, Folder 37)
- Loudon County, 1860 (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Louisa County, 1860 (Box 1, Folder 39)
- Madison County, 1860 (Box 1, Folder 40)
- Marion County, 1858 (Box 1, Folder 41)
- Mason County, 1857, 1859-1860 (Box 1, Folder 42)
- County (Box 2)
- County (Box 1)
- County (Box 1)
- County (Box 1)
- County (Box 1)
- County (Box 1)
- County (Box 1)
- County (Box 1)
- County (Box 1)
- County (Box 1)
- County (Box 1)
- County (Box 1)
- County (Box 1)
- County (Box 1)
- County (Box 1)
- County (Box 1)
- County (Box 1)
- County (Box 1)
- 